const gameThronesQuizData = [
    {
        QuizName: "Game of Thrones"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "1",
        Question: "Who was king of the Seven Kingdoms at the beginning of the main story?",
        Options: ["Viserys Targaryen", "Loras Tyrell", "Daenerys Targaryen", "Robert Baratheon"],
        Answer: "Robert Baratheon"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "2",
        Question: "Eddard belongs to what house?",
        Options: ["Stark", "Baratheon", "Martell", "Greyjoy"],
        Answer: "Stark"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "3",
        Question: "What is the house motto of house Lannister?",
        Options: ["Growing Strong", "Our Blades are Sharp", "Hear Me Roar", "A lannister always pays his debts"],
        Answer:"Hear Me Roar"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "4",
        Question: "There are nineteen fortified castles along the wall, but only three are manned. What are these three castles?",
        Options: ["Westwatch-by-the-sea, The Shadow Tower, Icemark", "The Shadow Tower, Castle Black, Eastwatch-by-the-sea", "Sable Hall, The Torches, Sentinel Stand", "Stonedoor, Hoarfrost Hill, Deep Lake"],
        Answer:"The Shadow Tower, Icemark"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "5",
        Question: "Which character has the nickname 'The Spider'?",
        Options: ["Varys", "Petyr", "Grey Worm", "Missandei"],
        Answer:"Varys"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "6",
        Question: "Who is the author of A Song of Ice and Fire?",
        Options: ["J.R.R Tolkien", "C.S. Lewis", "George R.R. Martin", "Frank Herbert"],
        Answer:"George R.R. Martin"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "7",
        Question: "Which of the Children of the Forest can speak the common tongue?",
        Options: ["Ash", "Scales", "Coals", "Leaf"],
        Answer:"Leaf"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "8",
        Question: "What are the creatures that compose the main bulk of the army of the dead?",
        Options: ["Wight", "White Walker", "Children of the Forest", "First Men"],
        Answer:"Wight"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "9",
        Question: "Who was the king of the giants?",
        Options: ["Dongo", "Wun Weg Wun Dar Wun", "Mag Mar Tun Doh Weg", "Tormund"],
        Answer:"Mag Mar Tun Doh Weg"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "10",
        Question: "Which dragon is the largest in the universe created by George R.R. Martin?",
        Options: ["Drogon", "Balerion", "Vhagar", "Vermithor"],
        Answer:"Balerion"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "11",
        Question: "Who was the leader of the Golden Company when Cersei hired them?",
        Options: ["Wes Borland", "Robert Westland", "Larys Strong", "Harry Strickland"],
        Answer:"Harry Strickland"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "12",
        Question: "How many kings did Varys serve?",
        Options: ["4", "5", "3", "6"],
        Answer:"4"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "13",
        Question: "Who was the fortune teller Cersei visited?",
        Options: ["Jenny the Newt", "Mirri Maz Duur", "Melisandre", "Maggie the Frog"],
        Answer:"Maggie the Frog"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "14",
        Question: "What is the name of Euron's ship?",
        Options: ["Snow", "Silence", "Bloodmoon", "Balerion"],
        Answer:"Silence"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "15",
        Question: "How many masters does Daenerys crucify after she took Meereen?",
        Options: ["211", "150", "163", "100"],
        Answer:"163"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "16",
        Question: "What is the tallest structure in the Sevon Kingdoms?",
        Options: ["Oldtown's High Tower", "The Wall", "The Eyrie", "Great Pyramid of Meereen"],
        Answer:"Oldtown's High Tower"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "17",
        Question: "Which Great House lived by the words, 'Family, Duty, Honor'?",
        Options: ["Martell", "Tully", "Tyrell", "Frey"],
        Answer:"Tully"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "18",
        Question: "Who says the famous quote, 'I drink and I know things'?",
        Options: ["Jaime Lannister", "Arya Stark", "Oberyn Martell", "Tyrion Lannister"],
        Answer:"Tyrion Lannister"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "19",
        Question: "What is Petyr Baelish's sigil?",
        Options: ["Rose", "Cross", "Mockingbird", "Five Fingered Hand"],
        Answer:"Mockingbird"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "20",
        Question: "In the show, who is the one that chopped jaime's hand off?",
        Options: ["Locke", "Selwyn", "Vargo Hoat", "Urswyck"],
        Answer:"Locke"
    }
]